We are all aware of the threats our planet is facing.
我们都清楚地球正面临着怎样的威胁。
Experts agree that it’s mainly us humans who are responsible for the destruction of the environment.
专家们一致认为，环境遭到破坏，主要责任在我们人类。
Activities such as mass farming and burning fossil fuels are taking their toll on our climate – and we’re suffering too through natural disasters such as flooding and more frequent droughts.
大规模农业耕作、燃烧化石燃料这类活动正在给气候造成严重损害，而我们也正承受着自然灾害带来的后果——洪水和愈发频繁的干旱。
One of the most destructive activities we are carrying out is cutting down forests - deforestation.
人类正在进行的最具破坏性的活动之一就是砍伐森林。
This is done for many reasons, such as providing wood for fuel, making land available for housing or for creating space for more cattle to graze on.
人们这么做的原因有很多，比如获取木材当燃料、腾出土地建造房屋，或是开辟更多空间让牛群吃草。
This has been most noticeable in Brazil, which is home to the world’s largest rainforest.
这一现象在巴西表现得尤为明显，因为这里有着全球最大的热带雨林。
Deforestation there has hit its highest rate in a decade, according to official data.
官方数据显示，巴西的森林砍伐率已经达到了十年来的最高值。
Over the course of a year, an area about five times the size of London has been destroyed.
在一年的时间里，大约五个伦敦面积大小的森林遭到了破坏。
The amount of deforestation in the Amazon and in other tropical regions has actually seen a decline but the figures are still large.
亚马逊流域以及其他热带地区的森林砍伐量实际上已经有所下降，但总量依然不容小觑。
Global Forest Watch say that in 2018, an area equivalent to 30 football fields were cut down every minute.
全球森林观察组织称，2018年，每分钟就有相当于30个足球场面积的森林被砍伐。
Frances Seymour from the World Resources Institute says that “If you look back over the last 18 years, it is clear that the overall trend is still upwards.
世界资源研究所的弗朗西斯·西摩表示：“回顾过去18年的情况，很明显整体趋势仍在恶化。
We are nowhere near winning this battle."
我们远未打赢这场战役。”
What’s special about places like the Amazon is that they are primary forests which exist in their original condition with some species of trees dating back thousands of years.
像亚马逊这样的地区有着独特之处，它们属于原生林，保持着原始的生态状态，其中一些树种的历史可以追溯到数千年以前。
This habitat is home to unique and rare animals and is critical for sustaining biodiversity.
这片栖息地是珍稀特有动物的家园，对维护生物多样性至关重要。
The BBC’s environment correspondent, Matt McGrath, says “These old forests really matter as stores of carbon dioxide, which is why the loss of 3.6 million hectares in 2018 is concerning.”
英国广播公司环境记者马特·麦格拉思表示：“这些古老的森林作为二氧化碳的储存库，有着不可替代的作用，这也是为什么2018年失去360万公顷森林的消息会引发担忧。”
Brazil has taken some steps to try and decrease deforestation by introducing government policies including fines for breaking land use regulations and clamping down on illegal logging.
巴西已经采取了一些措施来减少森林砍伐，出台了多项政府政策，包括对违反土地使用规定的行为处以罚款，以及严厉打击非法伐木行为。
And International campaigns to stop the trade of soy and beef farmed on deforested parts of the Amazon have also had a significant impact.
此外，国际社会发起了相关运动，禁止交易产自亚马逊毁林区的大豆和牛肉，这些举措也产生了显著的影响。
But meanwhile other parts of the world, such as Ghana and the Democratic Republic of Congo, are seeing dramatic increases.
但与此同时，世界上其他地区，比如加纳和刚果民主共和国，森林砍伐现象正急剧增多。
So it seems only political will and human conscience will tackle this problem and save planet Earth.
如此看来，或许只有凭借政治决心和人类良知，才能解决这个问题，拯救我们的地球家园。